<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><rss version='2.0'><channel><title>Hello Cobalt</title><link>http://booyaa.github.io/hello-cobalt/</link><description>A test blog for cobalt!</description><item><title>Snippet Test</title><link>http://booyaa.github.io/hello-cobalt/2017/snippet-test/index.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Glossier prism humblebrag excepteur, try-hard jianbing pariatur succulents pork belly non  XOXO small batch plaid echo park.  Keffiyeh tattooed shoreditch dreamcatcher raw denim.  Health goth asymmetrical aesthetic, mustache af heirloom prism adaptogen aute  hell of kogi placeat.  Bushwick enim sapiente, commodo iceland eiusmod incididunt plaid keytar retro bitters actually vape vero officia.  Portland enamel pin literally small batch kickstarter, ullamco scenester slow-carb pinterest in  tumeric offal.  Art party lyft next level, duis  put a bird on it adaptogen polaroid mollit  lumbersexual try-hard four loko locavore tacos migas tofu.  Bitters ramps next level iceland.Here&apos;s some &lt;/p&gt;
</description><guid>http://booyaa.github.io/hello-cobalt/2017/snippet-test/index.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 20:47:00 +0100</pubDate></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>http://booyaa.github.io/hello-cobalt/2016/first-post/index.html</link><description>&lt;p&gt;Heirloom hexagon selfies, bitters meditation elit mlkshk fashion axe irony.  Keffiyeh normcore biodiesel ullamco banjo.  Magna locavore chicharrones drinking vinegar helvetica, ex viral tofu flexitarian.  Neutra poutine etsy DIY, intelligentsia street art pop-up narwhal adipisicing hella fap direct trade.  Ennui nihil banjo, meh lo-fi deserunt  DIY pour-over gentrify XOXO.  8-bit pariatur chicharrones, fap keytar asymmetrical unicorn culpa  messenger bag glossier forage hell of.  Aliqua duis  cred aesthetic, sartorial semiotics jean shorts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><guid>http://booyaa.github.io/hello-cobalt/2016/first-post/index.html</guid><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 21:00:30 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>